# **Chase Fleming**

Mathematician

#### About

1431 Deerwood St
Columbia South Carolina
SC 29205 US

1 +1(864) 494-7378

flemingchase

### Coding

#### Intermediate

Python SAS and R

C/C++ Git

#### Office Sofware

#### Master

Microsoft Office Suite

Powerpoint, Excel, Word

# Typesetting

# Master

LaTex

#### Languages

English (Native speaker) Korean (Intermediate)

# Interests

#### **Mathematics**

Functional Analysis Set Theory Foundations of Quantum Mechanics

#### **Music Collecting**

Black Metal Death Metal Cassette & CDs

## Summary

I am a mathematics PhD student at the University of South Carolina under the advisorship of Dr. George Androulakis. My research interests include set theory, general topology, functional analysis, quantum information, and foundations of quantum mechanics.

#### Experience

#### Graduate Instructor

Throughout my time at UofSC, I have been an instructor of record. I have been a teaching assistant for Calculus I and Calculus II. I have been an instructor of record for Basic College Algebra, Caluclus for Social Science and Business Majors, and Discrete Math for Computer Science Majors.

05/2024 - 09/2024

08/2019 - Present

#### Mathematics Assessment of Prerequisites Troubleshooter

I assisted incoming students with their math placement exams during the summer. I was responsible for fielding students' problems with accessing the testing platform and resolving them in a timely fashion.

#### 04/2016 - 06/2016

08/2014 - 08/2019

08/2019 - Present

05/2022 - 05/2023

08/2023 - 06/2024

#### Scheduling Coordinator

I was responsible for constructing the tournament schedule for the main event and all side events during the 2016 National History Bee and Bowl held in Chicago, IL. My roles included programming a individual schedules for teams and individual participants, on site assistance, and interfacing with parents, teams, and participants.

#### Education

#### **Johns Hopkins University**

Bachelor of Arts Mathematics

#### **University of South Carolina**

PhD Mathematics

#### Volunteer

# University of South Carolina Math Department

Host of Fluid Dynamics

I was responsible for hosting the math department's sanctioned weekly social. I was responsible for helping first year students integrate into our department by introducing them professors and senior graduate students.

# Awards

# David L. Boren Fellowship

National Security Education Program

The Boren fellowship awards funding to graduate students in order to study critical languages. I was chosen for the 2023-2024 school year. I lived in Seoul, South Korea from August until June. While there, I participated in roughly 20 hours of language study per week at Sogang University's Korean Language Education Center. I went from having zero language skill to an intermediate speaker in this time frame.